Hi everyone, welcome to my channel.  My
name is Ben and I'm your insurance
partner.  So now let's talk about
manifests, medical secure or med secure.
With the rising cost of hospitalization
here in the Philippines, it really won't be enough
if your coverage is low.  Because
if your HMO coverage is low
, you have to really shell out money.
So if you are looking for high
coverage or high limits and at the
same time have special access or
better utilization then manolif
made secure is for you.
Let's first discuss the features of Med Secure.
So number one, he has extensive
medical care.  So what is
Medseicure's extensive medical care?  So number
one, it covers hospital confinement
before and after care.  also covers
emergency treatments and it covers
special procedures anywhere in the
Philippines.  One of the main features as
well as Med secure is that it covers high
medical coverage.  You can get high
medical coverage with annual benefit
limit from 1 million to 5 million.  Plus
Med Secure even has life
insurance protection.  You also have wide
access to accredited hospitals
partner with our medical network
provider which is value care.  And for
the non-accredited partners or
hospitals, reimbursement
options are available.  It's guaranteed renewal.  You
can get protection coverage up to 75
years old as long as the coverage is
paid on time.  It's very easy access
treatment.  Just present the digital card
or letter of authorization or LOA.  One
of the value added benefits of Med
Secure is that they have 247
telemedicine consoles or teleconsoles.
How much is Medse secure?  Med secure
is based on age.  For as low as Php60 a
day, for a 35 year old male, you can
get med secure.  So just imagine
how much is that monthly that's
roughly 2,000 to 3,000 it starts from
there.  So now you know the main
features of MedS Secure.  Let
's discuss each one in detail.  With
Med Secure, you can choose from three.
from plan 1 million, plan 2.5 million
and plan 5 million.  So let's discuss the
annual benefit limit.  With plan 1
M or plan 1 million, you can get 100,000
life insurance.  So in case of untimely
death of the insured,
your declared
beneficiaries will get 100,000.  Another feature of plan
1M is that it covers you regular private room
and board during your hospital stay up
to Php5,000.
For the 2.5M plan, you have
250,000
life insurance coverage.  For the room,
you're covered for large private up to
Php7,000.
For the plan 5M, you're covered
500,000 life insurance coverage.  And for
the room, you're covered executive suite
up to Php15,000.
So in short for the life insurance it's
10% of the annual benefit limit.  And for
the room and board during your hospital
stay, it depends on your plans whether it's 1M
, 2.5M or 5M.  You have free and
unlimited access to general
practitioners and family medicine
consults.  You can access this service by
Dr.  Anywhere app.  Another benefit is if
you're planning to consult with a
specialist in the Doctor Anywhere app, their specialists will have
lower rates or more discounts
if
you book a consultation versus the
usual regular Dr. membership.
Anywhere app.  Exclusive for Medcure
members.  One of the things I like most about
Medse Secure is that it has out-
patient care before and afterization.
So you can get reimbursement 60 days
prior to admission and 60 days after
admission up to your remaining
annual benefit limit.  Another feature that
I also liked about Medsecure is that they
also cover special procedure coverage.
Special procedures are usually the
most expensive.
Those are the tests that need to be done.
So what does
Med Secure's special procedure cover?  Here are the
few commonly utilized procedures
covered by Med Secure.  MRI, City
Scan, 2D Echo with Doppler,
chemotherapy, radiotherapy, kidney
dialysis.  Just a reminder, a
doctor's order and diagnosis are required
for this special procedure.  So let's
talk about those that are out of scope
of Med Secure or those that it doesn't
cover.  Number one is the
emergency treatment.  For emergency
treatment, it is not covered unless
he continues or proceeds to
regular confinement or admission.
But if the emergency treatment is due to
accident, for example dog bite or
dengue, he is covered with or
without hospital admission up to your
annual benefit limit.  Also,
we have what is called a waiting period term
for medically secure.  When it says waiting
period, this time frame or timeline is the
waiting period, after that, only then can
we or only then
can you use or claim it.  When
it says waiting period, it doesn't mean
he won't be covered.  We just have a
grace period or waiting period that we
have to wait before it can be availed
which is usually common among HMO
providers.  The good thing about Medse
Secure is that it's guaranteed renewal.  So
after the 12 month period, whatever
illnesses that you have, as long as
he is in school and can be handled by
your annual benefit limit, that will be covered.  Med
secure also covers you for annual
checkups.  So you'll get a free annual
checkup every year.  So we have plan for
plan 1, plan 2 for 2.5m and plan 3 for 5
coverages or tests included in plan
one.  Physical examination, chess x-ray,
urinalysis, fechaysis, CBC, FBS and
total cholesterol.  You can request
that, uh, depending on what the
nearest or accredited facility is
near you.  So for the complete
test, kindly screenshot for the other
plans.  Another very important feature of
Medse Secure is their app-based
claims experience.  So that means you can now
process after sales,
your HMO avail, and your claims right from the
app.  You can access your digital
card there.  You can request your LOA.  You can
schedule your annual checkups.  You can
file or request for reimbursements.  And
you can also track and see your
remaining coverage right there in the app.  Or
not?  He's very self-empowering, isn't he?
You're not the one who's going to ask anymore.   You
won't have to go back and forth
on your policy because you'll see
him there.  You are empowered to do things.
You can take a selfie for the impatient
care.  It covers you room and board
medical professional fees, surgeon and
anesthesiologist fees, operating room,
ICU and recovery room.  All covered as long as
he/she falls within your ABL or the annual
benefit limit.  I also do free
consultations.  I will
discuss it with you myself.  All you need to
do is just click the link below or
just message me here on my social
media accounts.  So if you want to know
more about life insurance, health
insurance, HMO and other types of
insurance, just like and follow
my channel.  And if you think
this video can help others, please
share it.